A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Finance, 1986-1998
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 34593], 1986-1994, Extent: 24 cu. ft. (24 boxes). (Box 1-24)
  - Attorney General's Office, 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Historic Resources, 1989 (Box 24)
  - DMC, 1988-1992 (Box 24)
  - Dept. of Education, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, 1992 (Box 24)
  - GMU, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Health Department, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Local Government Advisory Council, 1992-1993 (Box 24)
  - Museum of Natural History, 1993 (Box 24)
  - NSU, 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - ODU, 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Social Services Deficit (Box 24)
  - SCC Building, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Supreme Court, 1987 (Box 24)
  - VCU, 1987-1993 (Box 24)
  - VCCS, 1987-1992 (Box 24)
  - VMI, 1987-1992 (Box 24)
  - VPI and SU, 1987-1993 (Box 24)
  - VHDA, 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Treasury Dept., 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, VA State Library, 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Visually Handicapped, 1988-1993 (Box 24)
  - VSU, 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - College of William and Mary, 1987-1993 (Box 24)
  - Waste Management, 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 1990 (Box 24)
  - ACIR, 1986-1991 (Box 24)
  - Governor's Drug Policy, 1989-1991 (Box 24)
  - Applications, 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - BIDCO Work Group, 1989 (Box 24)
  - DIT Connectivity Project, 1988 June (Box 24)
  - VCU, CEBAF, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Chinese (Liaoning) Delegation (Box 24)
  - Capitol Square Master Plan (Box 24)
- Series II: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 34974], 1986-1994., Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 1-11)
  - Tax Policy Options, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Davis vs. Michigan Dept. of Treasury, 1989-1991 (Box 1-2)
  - Revenue Re-estimation Notebook, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Gubernatorial Data, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Base Budget Calculations, 1990-1992 (Box 3)
  - Pledge Bond Information, 1990 (Box 3)
  - TPS, Drug Program, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Presentations by Paul Timmreck (Sec. of Finance), 1987-1990 (Box 3)
  - Robb for Senate, Information, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Drug Program (Box 3)
  - Standards of Quality (Box 3)
  - Charitable Campaign, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Income tax, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Leadership Summit on Health Care, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of Administration, 1989-1992 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1989-1993 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1989-1993 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of Education, 1989-1993 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1989-1993 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1988-1993 (Box 4)
  - Early Retirement (Box 4)
  - Oil Overcharge, 1983-1993 (Box 4)
  - Memos to and from Secretaries, 1989-1992 (Box 4)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, 1989-1993 (Box 5)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, Violent Crime Commission, Anti-Crime Forum, 1993 June 22 (Box 5)
  - Secretary of Transportation, 1989-1993 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Office Correspondence, 1992 May-December (Box 5)
  - Memos to and from Secretaries, 1989-1993 (Box 5)
  - Northern Virginia Natural Gas Presentation (Deputy), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Memos to Agency Heads (Box 5)
  - NASBO Public Sector Consultants (Box 5)
  - NASBO Meetings, 1991 (Box 5)
  - NASBO Meetings, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Liaison Office, 1989-1993 (Box 6)
  - NASBO, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Governor's Constituent Mail, 1993 January-May (Box 6)
  - Governor's Constituent Mail, 1993 October-November (Box 6)
  - National Governor's Association, 1990-1992 (Box 6)
  - National Tax Association, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Commission on Virginia's Economic Recovery (Box 7)
  - College of William and Mary, Virginia Business Report, 1988-1990 (Box 7)
  - Virginia State Parks, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Tax Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 7)
  - Lottery Miscellaneous, 1989-1992 (Box 7)
  - Workers Compensation, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Council on Information Management Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Financial Proposal, 1986-1988 (Box 7)
  - Spousal Offset under Social Security, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Job Class Regrades, 1988-1992 (Box 7)
  - Shared Provider Financing, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Compensation, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Capital Budget, 1992-1994 (Box 8)
  - Federal Budget Deficit, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Carry forwards, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Higher Education, 1986-1992 (Box 8)
  - Commission on Educational Opportunity, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Decentralization, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Governor Wilder's Open House, Southwestern Virginia, 1993 April 17 (Box 9)
  - Governor Wilder's Open House, Northern Virginia, 1993 January 23 (Box 9)
  - Governor Wilder's Open House, Harrisonburg, 1992 November 14 (Box 9)
  - Governor Wilder's Open House, Richmond, 1992 October 24 (Box 9)
  - Governor Wilder's Open House, General (Box 9)
  - Revenue Forecasting, 1988-1990 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Office Constituent Letters, 1993 June (Box 9)
  - Action requiring Governor's Involvement, 1991-1993 (Box 9)
  - Clinch Valley Seed Project, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Housing Fund, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Statewide Shell Building Initiative (Box 9)
  - Urban Town Meetings (Box 9)
  - Kiptopeke Beach Campground, 1991 (Box 9)
  - C & P Tricon Proposal, 1991 (Box 9)
  - NGA Cabinet Retreat (Box 9)
  - Statewide Black Leadership, 1989 May (Box 9)
  - Legislative Budget Requests, 1991-1993 (Box 9)
  - Corning Glass, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Cultural Laureate Foundation, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1988-1992 (Box 9)
  - Commission on Virginia Economic Recovery, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - UVA, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - VHDA, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - VML, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Dillon Commission, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Dykes vs. NVTC (Box 10)
  - VPBA, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Budget Cut Letters, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Budget Reduction Plans, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - Budget, Non state agencies, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Budget Press Package, 1989 January (Box 10)
  - General Fund Revenue Estimates, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Budget Bill Executive Amendments, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - Budget Process, 1988-1990 (Box 10)
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Budget papers, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - Budget fees, 1994 (Box 10)
  - State and Local Legal Center, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - SEAA, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - NGA, 1990 (Box 10)
  - VEA, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Capital Projects, Lottery, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Fiscal Close, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Higher Education, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Tech, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - Paperwork Reduction, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Commission on Efficiency, Finance Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Commission on Efficiency, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Privatization of Government Services, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Budget Symposium, 1992 November (Box 11)
  - Governor's Budget Symposium, 1993 June (Box 11)
  - Symposium Background (Box 11)
  - Defense Cuts, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Tax, Local Taxing Authority, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Tax, Management Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Tax, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Tax, Real Estate Tax, 1990 (Box 11)
- Series III: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 35256], 1988-1994., Extent: 4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 1-4)
  - Joint Money Committtee Meetings, 1990 August 17 (Box 1)
  - Joint Money Committtee Meetings, 1991 January 10 (Box 1)
  - Joint Money Committtee Meetings, 1991 December 16 (Box 1)
  - Joint Money Committtee Meetings, 1992 August 14 (Box 1)
  - Joint Money Committtee Meetings, 1992 November 16 (Box 1)
  - Joint Money Committtee Meetings, 1992 December 21 (Box 1)
  - Joint Money Committtee Meetings, 1993 August 23 (Box 1)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 1991 December (Box 1)
  - Equipment Leasing Program, Treasury Board, 1988-1991 (Box 1)
  - SNAP, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Security for Public Deposits Act, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Non general Fund Interest (Box 1)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Virginia College Building Authority, 1987-1993 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Public School Authority, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Treasury Dept. Goals and Objectives, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Enhanced Collection Systems, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Tax Issue Papers (Box 1)
  - Revenues, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Budget Amendments, Finance, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Budget Amendments, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Fiscal Policy Development, Finance Agencies, 1992-1994 (Box 2)
  - Budget, Capital, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
  - Budget, Public Hearings, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Capital Outlay, G.O. Bond Bill, 1992-1994 (Box 2)
  - Governor's Veto, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Budget, Revenue Shortfall, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
  - Horse Center, 1992 (Box 2)
  - VCBA, Tuition Revenue Bond Proposal (Box 2)
  - Alternative Financing Guidelines, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Republican Truth Committee, Social Security (Box 2)
  - $15 M Additional to Education, 1991 October 21 (Box 2)
  - Frontier Culture Museum, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Finance Legislation Talking Points, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Christopher Newport College, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Joint Money Committee Meeting, 1990 August 17 (Box 2)
  - Joint Money Committee Meeting, 1992 January 8 (Box 2)
  - JLARC, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
  - Job Class Regrades, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - James Madison University, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Doneski vs. Comptroller, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Haysi Dam, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Lottery Building, Proposed 9th and Broad, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lottery Building, 900 East Main Street, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Form 1099, Information Return Requirements, 1990-1993 (Box 2)
  - General Services, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Cost Study, Capital Outlay, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Treasury Loans, 1988-1990 (Box 2)
  - Public Safety, 1990-1993 (Box 2)
  - VPBA, Main Street Station> (Box 2)
  - Route 58, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Treasury, Interim Financing, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Literary Fund, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Tax Amnesty (Box 2)
  - Finance Weekly Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 2)
  - Finance Legislative Proposals, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Budget, Money, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - Budget Amendments, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Budget, Employee Comp Benefits, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - College Presidents' Meeting, 1993 September 23 (Box 3)
  - Compliance Initiative, 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Congressional Delegation Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 3)
  - Decentralization, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Emergency Services (Box 3)
  - Executive Memo, Privatization, 1988 January (Box 3)
  - Explore, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Federal Budget, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Office Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Higher Ed Equipment Trust Fund, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Memos to Governor, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Publications Cost Study, 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Science Museum, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Shenandoah Armory, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Paul W. Timmreck speeches, 1990 May-1993 May (Box 4)
- IV: Correspondence and subject files, 1994-1998 [Accession 35871], 1994-1998, Extent: 4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 1-4)
  - General Assembly Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Finance, Customer Service Plans (Box 1)
  - Secretary Timmreck's Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 1)
  - Secretary Tillett's Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Attorney General's Office Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Information, 1994 March (Box 1)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Information, 1997 February (Box 1)
  - Requests for Information under FOIA, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Council on Information Management (Box 1)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Dept. of General Services Correspondence (Box 1)
  - House Appropriations Committee Correspondence (Box 1)
  - JLARC Correspondence (Box 1)
  - John Tyler Community College Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Virginia Liaison Office Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Lottery Dept. Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Salary regrades (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education in Virginia Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Science Museum of Virginia Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Supreme Court Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Triple Cross Connections Correspondence (Box 1)
  - University of Virginia Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Virginia College Building Authority Correspondence (Box 1)
  - VELA-VSAA Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Virginia Community College System Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Virginia Geographic Information Network Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Accounts, Direct Deposits Stubs Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Accounts, Relocation reimbursement study (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Accounts, Third Party Administration (Box 1)
  - "Ask Governor Allen" (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Accounts Receivable Issues (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Compliance Initiative (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Enhanced Collection System (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Mail Order Sales Tax (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Privatization Opportunities (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Meeting with Commissioners of Revenue, 1997 March (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, "Unalterable Cash Register Tapes" (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Strategic Plan (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, "Performance standards for field auditors" (Box 1)
  - Commonwealth Bond Issues (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Transfer of Building from DMV (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Taxation, Virginia Medical Savings Account Act (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Treasury, Debt Capacity Advisory Committee (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Treasury, Investment Program and Policies (Box 2)
  - Combined Virginia Campaign (Box 2)
  - Governor's subject files, 1994 February-June (Box 2)
  - Governor's subject files, 1994 July-1995 January (Box 2)
  - Governor's subject files, 1995 February-July (Box 2)
  - Governor's subject files, 1995 August-1996 February (Box 2)
  - Governor's subject files, 1996 March-1997 March (Box 2)
  - Governor's subject files, 1997 April-November (Box 2)
  - Secretary of Finance, Customer Service Forum, 1994 August 31 (Box 2)
  - Customer Service Plans (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Decentralization Pilot Projects (Box 2)
  - Financial World, Fiscal Survey of the States (Box 2)
  - Health Insurance Trust Fund (Box 2)
  - Lag Pay Memorandums (Box 2)
  - Management Standards, Higher Education (Box 2)
  - State and Local mandates (Box 2)
  - Questionnaires, Surveys (Box 2)
  - Presentations, Secretary Timmreck (Box 2)
  - Presentations, Secretary Tillett (Box 2)
  - Speeches, Secretary Tillett, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Presentations, Joint Money Committees, 1994-1997 (Box 3)
  - Revenue Data, 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Revenue Data, 1994 July-December (Box 3)
  - Revenue Data, 1995 January-June (Box 3)
  - Revenue Data, 1995 July-December (Box 3)
  - Revenue Data, 1996 January-June (Box 3)
  - Revenue Data, 1996 July-December (Box 3)
  - Revenue Report, 1995 January-June (Box 3)
  - Revenue Report, 1995 July-December (Box 3)
  - Revenue Report, 1997 January-June (Box 3)
  - Revenue Report, 1997 July-December (Box 3)
  - Revenue Report, Mid-session Forecast, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Revenue Report, Mid-session Forecast, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Revenue Report, Mid-session Forecast, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Revenue Stabilization Fund (Box 3)
  - Correspondence with other Cabinet Secretaries (Box 3)
  - Correspondence with General Assembly, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence with General Assembly, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence with General Assembly, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence with General Assembly, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office (Box 3)
  - Secretary Timmreck Correspondence, 1994 February-May (Box 3)
  - Secretary Timmreck Correspondence, 1994 June-September (Box 3)
  - Secretary Timmreck Correspondence, 1994 October-December (Box 3)
  - Secretary Timmreck Correspondence, 1995 January-March (Box 3)
  - Secretary Timmreck Correspondence, 1995 April-June (Box 3)
  - Secretary Timmreck Correspondence, 1995 July-December (Box 3)
  - Secretary Timmreck Correspondence, 1996 January-July (Box 3)
  - Secretary Tillett Correspondence, 1996 August-December (Box 4)
  - Secretary Tillett Correspondence, 1997 January-March (Box 4)
  - Secretary Tillett Correspondence, 1997 April-May (Box 4)
  - Secretary Tillett Correspondence, 1997 June-July (Box 4)
  - Secretary Tillett Correspondence, 1997 August-1998 January (Box 4)